Guide to the Meyer Lissner Papers, 1903-1923 (inclusive), 1910-1920 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections
Meyer Lissner Papers,
1903-1923 (inclusive), 1910-1920 (bulk)
Lissner, Meyer, 1871-1930.
Special Collections M0070
30 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Correspondence, legal and financial papers, photographs, clippings and miscellaneous printed material including circulars, new releases, speeches, and political hand bills. The papers are predominantly political with particular emphasis on the non-partisan reform movement in Los Angeles beginning about 1906, the organization of the Lincoln-Roosevelt Republican League (1907), and the Progressive movement especially in California through Hiram Johnson's presidential campaign (1920).
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the Lissner family, 1934, 1963.
Scope and Content Note
The Meyer Lissner Papers consist of approximately 40,000 items from 1903 to 1923. Most of the material falls between 1910 and 1920 and is primarily in the form of correspondence. There are also legal and financial papers, pamphlets, clippings, miscellaneous printed matter (form letters, news releases, political hand bills, etc.) and photographs.
The subject matter is almost entirely political. It shows the growth and decline of the Progressive movement, particularly in California; the formation of the Lincoln-Roosevelt Republican League; and the Los Angeles non-partisan reform movement, to name only a few. The correspondence between notable political figures either in the lime-light or behind-the-scenes is very open and frank. Goals, ideals and disappointments are discussed at length, revealing as much about personalities as the times. The letters between Lissner, Hiram Johnson and Chester Rowell are excellent examples. Campaign policies on local, state and national levels is another interesting subject. This material shows the inner workings of a political organization, the tactical maneuvering and the interplay and manipulation of the various participants.
A few items may be found of a business or personal nature, relating to the law firm, real estate interests and family. These form a very small percentage and give only a hint of Lissner's private life. Even these usually discuss public issues as well as private affairs.
The reference and printed materials cover a variety of subjects in which Lissner was interested. Among these are topics related to the various boards or commissions on which he served, such as the Los Angeles Public Utilities Board and the California Industrial Accident Commission. As editor of the California Outlook, organ of the Progressives in that state, he collected typescripts of articles, news releases and clippings and corresponded with many subscribers, advertisers, trustees and contributors. Other materials show interest in the various clubs, political and social, in which he held membership. But here too the emphasis is political and includes information on public figures, political parties and clubs, the Los Angeles charter revision, the conflict with various newspapers on political matters and the Southern Pacific machine.
The correspondents are many and varied, making a complete listing, even of the more important ones, almost impossible. The most important single correspondent for both bulk of material and content is Hiram W. Johnson. Lissner was one of a number of men who pushed Johnson to political prominence and one of the few Progressives who remained loyal after the death of that movement and Johnson's apparent dessertion of its ideals. Related to Johnson's correspondence and important in its own right is the material pertaining to his gubernatorial and senatorial campaigns and particularly his 1920 presidential campaign. A few other important names are: Chester Rowell, Edgar A. Luce, John M. Eshleman, -dwin T. Earl, Francis J. Heney, William D. Stephens, C.C. Young, William Allen White, Theodore Roosevelt, Robert M. LaFollette, Harold L. Ickes and George W. Perkins. The list includes politicians on every level of government, newspapermen and publishers, business and professional men and women, civil servants and civic leaders. Most of these are of particular importance in California, but there are many of national interest and prominence.
Biographical Note
1871, June 16 born in San Francisco; son of Louis and Mathilda (Block) Lissner. education: public grammar and high school in Oakland.
c. 1886 began successful jewelry and pawnshop business.
1896, August 12 married Ermine Greenhood of Okland; three children: Louis Meyer, Jay Greenhood and Aline Mathilda.
1898-1899 Los Angeles Law School.
1899 practiced law in Los Angeles, first 6 years as partner of Edgar W. Camp, later Joseph L. Lewinsohn.
1906 organizer and secretary of Non-Partisan City Central Committee (of Los Angeles).
1906-1910 member of the executive committee of the Municipal League of Los Angeles. (2nd vice president in 1909.)
1907 an organizer of the Lincoln-Roosevelt Republican League in California. (chairman of Los Angeles County Executive Committee 1908, vice president, 1910.)
1907 secretary and organizer of Owens River Campaign Committee.
1907 organizer of City Club of Los Angeles. (member of the Board of Governers, vice president, 1908 and president, 1911.)
1909 president of the Good Government Organization.
1909-1911 organizer and secretary of the Good Government Fund.
1909-1911 member of the executive committee of the Direct Legislation League of California.
1909-1911 president of the Board of Public Utilities, City of Los Angeles.
1909-1916 member of executive committee of National Municipal League, 1909-1916.
1917 vice president of National Municipal League
1910-1916 chairman of California Republican State Central Committee.
1912-1916 member of National Executive Committee, Progressive Party (or Progressive National Com.)
1914-1917 editor of California Outlook
1915-1919 and 1928 member of California Industrial Accident Commission.
1921-1925 member of U.S. Shipping Board (resigned 1925.)
1930, July 28 died.
Access Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Anderson, George B.; Bancroft, Philip, 1881-; Baumgartner, J. P.; Chenoweth, L. E. (Lawrence E.); Dickson, E. A.; Heney, Francis J., 1859-1937.; Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964.; Hughes, Charles Evans, 1862-1948.; Ickes, Harold L. (Harold LeClair), 1874-1952.; Johnson, Hiram Warren, 1866-1945.; Kent, William, 1864-1928.; Krehbiel, Henry Edward, 1854-1923.; La Follette, Robert M. (Robert Marion), 1855-1925.; Lewinsohn, Joseph L.; Lissner, Meyer, 1871-1930.; Luce, Edgar A., 1881-; Mc Cabe, Alexander.; Nelles, Fred C.; Neylan, John Francis, 1885-1960.; Older, Fremont, 1856-1935.; Otis, Harrison Gray, 1837-1917.; Perkins, George W., 1862-1920.; Pinchot, Gifford, 1865-1946.; Pope, Arthur Upham, 1881-1969.; Robinson, Leo S.; Rolph, James.; Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919.; Rowell, Chester Harvey, 1867-1948.; Russell, Charles Edward, 1860-1941.; Shoup, Paul, 1874-1946.; Spreckels, Rudolph.; Stephens, William D. 1859-1944.; Stone, George W.; Taft, William h. (William Howard), 1857-1930.; Thompson, Newton Wayland, 1882-; White, William Allen, 1868-1944.; Willard, C. D.; Wilson, Woodrow, 1856-1924.; Woodruff, Clinton Rogers, 1868-?.; Young, Clement Calhoun, 1869-1947.; California Railroad Commission.; Hetch Hetchy Reservior (Calif.); League of Nations.; Lincoln-Roosevelt Republican League.; Los Angeles.; Progressive Party.; Sierra Club.; Southern Pacific Company.; Title Insurance and Trust Co. (Los Angeles); Ballot.; Democratic Party--California.; Eight-hour movement.; Election law.; Elections, nonpartisan.; Employer's liability--California.; Initiative, Right of.; Insurance, unemployment.; Prohibition--California.; Primaries.; Proportional representation.; Recall--California.; Republican Party--California.; Single tax.; Socialism.; Women--Suffrage.
Collection Contents
- Series 1. Correspondence Out, 1909-1923
  Arranged chronologically overall and alphabetically within each date.
  The majority of this material is carbon copies, usually not signed and often not even initialed. Some of these were probably not by Lissner. According to Alice Rose it must be noted that carbon copies of letters included (1907-1909) were signed by Charles W. Bell, Sidney A. Butler, William Justus Rice, Frank G. Henderson and members of the Lissner office staff as well as Meyer Lissner. In some cases letters by Louis M. Lissner and Joseph L. Lewinsohn have been included where they are acting as agents of the law firm.
  - 1903-1904 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1905 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1906 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - January-June 1907 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - July-September 1907 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - October 1-15 1907 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - October 15-31 1907 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - November 1907 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - December 1907 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - January 1908 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - February 1908 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - March 1908 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - April 1-14 1908 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - April 16-30 1908 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - May 1908 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - June 1908 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - July 1908 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - August-September 1908 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - October-November 1908 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - December 1908 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 1909 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - February-October 1910 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - November 1-23 1910 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - November 25-30 1910 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - December 1-12 1910 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - December 13-30 1910 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - January 1-10 1911 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - January 18-23 1911 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - January 24-30 1911 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - January 31 1911 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - February 1-7 1911 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - February 8-10 1911 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - February 11-13 1911 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - February 14-16 1911 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - February 17-24 1911 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - March 1-10 1911 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - March 11-20 1911 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - March 21-31 1911 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - April 1911 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - May 1911 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - June 1-16 1911 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - June 17-30 1911 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - July 1911 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - August-September 1911 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - October 1911 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - November 1-15 1911 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - November 16-30 1911 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - December 1-15 1911 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - December 16-30 1911 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - January 1-12 1912 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - January 13-17 1912 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - January 18-31 1912 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - February 1-12 1912 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - February 13-27 1912 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - March 1-13 1912 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - March 14-20 1912 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - March 21-30 1912 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - April 1-6 1912 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - April 8-15 1912 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - April 16-20 1912 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - April 21-25 1912 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - April 26-30 1912 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - May 1-10 1912 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - May 11-20 1912 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - May 21-27 1912 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - May 28-31 1912 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - June 1-5 1912 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - June 6-8 1912 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - June 10-29 1912 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - July 1-17 1912 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - July 19-24 1912 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - July 25-31 1912 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - August 2-22 1912 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - August 23-26 1912 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - August 27-30 1912 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - September 2-20 1912 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - September 21-23 1912 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - September 24-30 1912 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - October 1-9 1912 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - October 10-14 1912 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - October 15-21 1912 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - October 22-31 1912 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - November 1-9 1912 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - November 11-19 1912 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - November 20-30 1912 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - December 2-7 1912 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - December 9-17 1912 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - December 18-31 1912 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - January 2-10 1913 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - January 11-20 1913 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - January 21-31 1913 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - February 1-14 1913 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - February 18-28 1913 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - March 1-10 1913 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - March 11-18 1913 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - March 19-31 1913 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - April 3-9 1913 (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - April 11-21 1913 (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - April 22-29 1913 (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - May 1913 (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - June 3-10 1913 (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - June 11-21 1913 (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - June 23-30 1913 (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - July-October 1913 (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - November 3-13 1913 (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - November 14-20 1913 (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - November 21-29 1913 (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - December 1-10 1913 (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - December 11-17 1913 (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - December 18-31 1913 (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - January-February 1914 (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - March-June 1914 (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - August-December 1914 (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - January 2-11 1915 (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - January 12-30 1915 (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - February 2-11 1915 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - February 13-20 1915 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - February 23-26 1915 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - March 2-9 1915 (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - March 10-19 1915 (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - March 20-31 1915 (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - April 1-15 1915 (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - April 20-30 1915 (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - May 1-13 1915 (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - May 14-19 1915 (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - May 20-31 1915 (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - June 1-17 1915 (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - June 18-30 1915 (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - July 1-13 1915 (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - July 16-31 1915 (Box 7, Folder 130)
  - August 2-5 1915 (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - August 6-11 1915 (Box 7, Folder 132)
  - August 12-19 1915 (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - August 20-31 1915 (Box 7, Folder 134)
  - September 1-21 1915 (Box 7, Folder 135)
  - September 22-30 1915 (Box 7, Folder 136)
  - October 1-14 1915 (Box 7, Folder 137)
  - October 16-30 1915 (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - November 1-10 1915 (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - November 11-18 1915 (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - November 22-30 1915 (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - December 1915 (Box 8, Folder 142)
  - January 3-13 1916 (Box 8, Folder 143)
  - January 14-29 1916 (Box 8, Folder 144)
  - February 1-12 1916 (Box 8, Folder 145)
  - February 14-29 1916 (Box 8, Folder 146)
  - March 1916 (Box 8, Folder 147)
  - April 5-10 1916 (Box 8, Folder 148)
  - April 12-30 1916 (Box 8, Folder 149)
  - May 1-15 1916 (Box 8, Folder 150)
  - May 16-28 1916 (Box 8, Folder 151)
  - June 1916 (Box 8, Folder 152)
  - July 3-15 1916 (Box 8, Folder 153)
  - July 18-31 1916 (Box 8, Folder 154)
  - August 1-8 1916 (Box 8, Folder 155)
  - August 9-14 1916 (Box 8, Folder 156)
  - August 15-18 1916 (Box 8, Folder 157)
  - August 19-30 1916 (Box 8, Folder 158)
  - September 1-12 1916 (Box 8, Folder 159)
  - September 15-29 1916 (Box 8, Folder 160)
  - October 2-12 1916 (Box 8, Folder 161)
  - October 13-30 1916 (Box 8, Folder 162)
  - November 2-14 1916 (Box 8, Folder 163)
  - November 15-29 1916 (Box 8, Folder 164)
  - December 1-30 1916 (Box 8, Folder 165)
  - January 2-31 1917 (Box 9, Folder 166)
  - February 1-10 1917 (Box 9, Folder 167)
  - February 14-19 1917 (Box 9, Folder 168)
  - February 20-28 1917 (Box 9, Folder 169)
  - March 1-9 1917 (Box 9, Folder 170)
  - March 12-22 1917 (Box 9, Folder 171)
  - March 23-31 1917 (Box 9, Folder 172)
  - April 2-13 1917 (Box 9, Folder 173)
  - April 14-30 1917 (Box 9, Folder 174)
  - May 1-14 1917 (Box 9, Folder 175)
  - May 17-23 1917 (Box 9, Folder 176)
  - May 24-31 1917 (Box 9, Folder 177)
  - June 1-28 1917 (Box 9, Folder 178)
  - July 1917 (Box 9, Folder 179)
  - August 1917 (Box 9, Folder 180)
  - September 1917 (Box 9, Folder 181)
  - October 1917 (Box 9, Folder 182)
  - November 1917 (Box 9, Folder 183)
  - December 1917 (Box 9, Folder 184)
  - January 1918 (Box 9, Folder 185)
  - February-March 1918 (Box 9, Folder 186)
  - April 1918 (Box 9, Folder 187)
  - May 2-20 1918 (Box 9, Folder 188)
  - May 21-31 1918 (Box 10, Folder 189)
  - June 1-12 1918 (Box 10, Folder 190)
  - June 13-29 1918 (Box 10, Folder 191)
  - July 1-5 1918 (Box 10, Folder 192)
  - July 6-30 1918 (Box 10, Folder 193)
  - August 1918 (Box 10, Folder 194)
  - September 1918 (Box 10, Folder 195)
  - October 1918 (Box 10, Folder 196)
  - November 1-19 1918 (Box 10, Folder 197)
  - November 20-29 1918 (Box 10, Folder 198)
  - December 1918 (Box 10, Folder 199)
  - [1918] (Box 10, Folder 200)
  - January-February 1919 (Box 10, Folder 201)
  - March 1919 (Box 10, Folder 202)
  - April 1919 (Box 10, Folder 203)
  - May 1-13 1919 (Box 10, Folder 204)
  - May 14-31 1919 (Box 10, Folder 205)
  - June-July 1919 (Box 10, Folder 206)
  - August 1919 (Box 10, Folder 207)
  - September 1919 (Box 10, Folder 208)
  - October 4-10 1919 (Box 10, Folder 209)
  - October 11-21 1919 (Box 10, Folder 210)
  - October 22 1919 (Box 10, Folder 211)
  - October 23-29 1919 (Box 10, Folder 212)
  - November 1-11 1919 (Box 11, Folder 212)
  - November 12-28 1919 (Box 11, Folder 213)
  - December 1-10 1919 (Box 11, Folder 214)
  - December 11-29 1919 (Box 11, Folder 215)
  - January 2-16 1920 (Box 11, Folder 216)
  - January 17-31 1920 (Box 11, Folder 217)
  - February 1-11 1920 (Box 11, Folder 218)
  - February 12-28 1920 (Box 11, Folder 219)
  - March 1-15 1920 (Box 11, Folder 220)
  - March 16-25 1920 (Box 11, Folder 221)
  - March 27-31 1920, April 1920 (Box 11, Folder 222)
  - May 1-15 1920 (Box 11, Folder 223)
  - May 17-31 1920 (Box 11, Folder 224)
  - June 1-30 1920 (Box 11, Folder 225)
  - July 1-19 1920 (Box 11, Folder 226)
  - July 20-31 1920 (Box 11, Folder 227)
  - August 2-9 1920 (Box 11, Folder 228)
  - August 10-16 1920 (Box 11, Folder 229)
  - August 17-31 1920 (Box 11, Folder 230)
  - September 1-15 1920 (Box 11, Folder 231)
  - September 16-30 1920 (Box 11, Folder 232)
  - October 1-13 1920 (Box 12, Folder 233)
  - October 14-30 1920 (Box 12, Folder 234)
  - November 1-10 1920 (Box 12, Folder 235)
  - November 11-18 1920 (Box 12, Folder 236)
  - November 20-30 1920 (Box 12, Folder 237)
  - December 1-10 1920 (Box 12, Folder 238)
  - December 13-31 1920 (Box 12, Folder 239)
  - January 3-31 1921 (Box 12, Folder 240)
  - January 14-31 1921 (Box 12, Folder 241)
  - February 1921 (Box 12, Folder 242)
  - March 1-14 1921 (Box 12, Folder 243)
  - March 15-30 1921 (Box 12, Folder 244)
  - April 1921 (Box 12, Folder 245)
  - May 2-10 1921 (Box 12, Folder 246)
  - May 11-31 1921 (Box 12, Folder 247)
  - June 1-9 1921 (Box 12, Folder 248)
  - June 10 1921 (Box 12, Folder 249)
  - June 11-28 1921 (Box 12, Folder 250)
  - July-September 1921 [1921], November-December 1922, January 1923 (Box 12, Folder 251)
- Series 2. Correspondence In, 1903-1923.
  Arranged alphabetically overall and chronologically for each individual correspondent.
  This is a general correspondence file and includes many letters written to persons other than Lissner. There are corporate as well as individual entries in this file so when looking for correspondence by a person, one should also refer to the organization and/or companies with which he was connected. This may also be used in the opposite way, i.e. when interested in a particular organization to look under the names of the various organization officers as well. Government organizations on state and local levels in most cases may be found under the name of the state, county or city, then alphabetically by key word. For the Lincoln-Roosevelt League, Republican and Progressive party material etc., particularly on the county level, refer also to the location. Businesses, clubs etc. generally are found under their own names if in Los Angeles and under location names (first word of national organization) if not in Los Angeles: i.e. City Club of Los Angeles, but New York City Club; Municipal League of Los Angeles, but National Municipal League.
  - Ab-Al (Box 12, Folder 252)
  - Am-Ar (Box 12, Folder 253)
  - As-Av (Box 12, Folder 254)
  - Avery, Russ (Box 12, Folder 255)
  - Bancroft, Philip #11910-April 1912 (Box 13, Folder 256)
  - Bancroft, Philip #2May-September 1912 (Box 13, Folder 257)
  - Bancroft, Philip #3October-December 1912 (Box 13, Folder 258)
  - Bancroft, Philip #41913, 1915, 1917 (Box 13, Folder 259)
  - Bab-Bard (Box 13, Folder 260)
  - Barh-Bau (Box 13, Folder 261)
  - Baumgartner, J.P.1910-1921 (Box 13, Folder 262)
  - Bea-Beh (Box 13, Folder 263)
  - Beasly, W.A.--Sterritt Case1917-1921 (Box 13, Folder 264)
  - Beatty, J.A.1907-1912 (Box 13, Folder 265)
  - Bel (Box 13, Folder 266)
  - Bem-Bev (Box 13, Folder 267)
  - Bi-Bla (Box 13, Folder 268)
  - Ble-Bly (Box 13, Folder 269)
  - Bir-Bos (Box 13, Folder 270)
  - Bou-Boy (Box 13, Folder 271)
  - Bra-Bro (Box 13, Folder 272)
  - Bru-Burd (Box 13, Folder 273)
  - Burk-By (Box 13, Folder 274)
  - Cab-Cau (Box 14, Folder 275)
  - California A (Box 14, Folder 276)
  - California B-F (Box 14, Folder 277)
  - California H-I (Box 14, Folder 278)
  - California #1 Industrial Accident Commission1913, 1916, 1917 (Box 14, Folder 279)
  - California #2 Industrial Accident Commission1918-1921 (Box 14, Folder 280)
    Department of Safety 1917, 1919
  - California L-T (Box 14, Folder 281)
  - California Railroad Commission (Box 14, Folder 282)
  - Camp, E.W. (Box 14, Folder 283)
  - Carnahan, H.L. (Box 14, Folder 284)
  - Ce-Chan (Box 14, Folder 285)
  - Chamberlain, S. (Box 14, Folder 286)
  - Chap-Chu (Box 14, Folder 287)
  - Ci (Box 14, Folder 288)
  - City Club of Los Angeles (Box 14, Folder 289)
  - Cla-Clark (Box 14, Folder 290)
  - Clarke-Clo (Box 14, Folder 291)
  - Coo-Coc (Box 14, Folder 292)
  - Cod-Col (Box 14, Folder 293)
  - Colby, W.E. (Box 14, Folder 294)
  - Com-Cool (Box 15, Folder 295)
  - Commonwealth Club of San Francisco (Box 15, Folder 296)
  - Coom-Cox (Box 15, Folder 297)
  - Cra-Cri (Box 15, Folder 298)
  - Cro-Cu (Box 15, Folder 299)
  - Dag-Dau (Box 15, Folder 300)
  - Davis A-N (Box 15, Folder 301)
  - Davis, J.B.F. & Son (Box 15, Folder 302)
  - Davis 0-Day (Box 15, Folder 303)
  - De (Box 15, Folder 304)
  - Detrick, C.R. (Box 15, Folder 305)
  - Devlin, F.R. (Box 15, Folder 306)
  - Di (Box 15, Folder 307)
  - Dickson, E.A. #1 1907-1909 (Box 15, Folder 308)
  - Dickson, E.A. #2 1910-1913, 1916, 1917 (Box 15, Folder 309)
  - Dixon, J.M. (Box 15, Folder 310)
  - Do-Dy (Box 15, Folder 311)
  - Drew, A.M. (Box 15, Folder 312)
  - Ea-Eg (Box 15, Folder 313)
  - Earl, E.T. (Box 15, Folder 314)
  - Edson, K.P. (Box 15, Folder 315)
  - Ei-El (Box 16, Folder 316)
  - Em-Ey (Box 16, Folder 317)
  - Eshleman, J.M. (Box 16, Folder 318)
  - Fa (Box 16, Folder 319)
  - Fe (Box 16, Folder 320)
  - Fels, J. (Box 16, Folder 321)
  - Fi (Box 16, Folder 322)
  - Fischer, W.H. (Box 16, Folder 323)
  - Fl (Box 16, Folder 324)
  - Fleishhacker, R. (Box 16, Folder 325)
  - Fo-Franc (Box 16, Folder 326)
  - Frank-Fras (Box 16, Folder 327)
  - Fre-Fu (Box 16, Folder 328)
  - French, W.J. (Box 16, Folder 329)
  - Ga (Box 16, Folder 330)
  - Ge-Gi (Box 16, Folder 331)
  - Gl-Gra (Box 16, Folder 332)
  - Good Government Organization and Fund (Box 16, Folder 333)
  - Gre (Box 16, Folder 334)
  - Gri-Gu (Box 16, Folder 335)
  - Ha-Harr (Box 17, Folder 336)
  - Hamilton, J.J. (Box 17, Folder 337)
  - Hart-Hav (Box 17, Folder 338)
  - Haw-Hec (Box 17, Folder 339)
  - Haynes, J.R. (Box 17, Folder 340)
  - Hays, W.H. (Box 17, Folder 341)
  - Hef-Her (Box 17, Folder 342)
  - Heney, F.J. #11907-1908 (Box 17, Folder 343)
  - Heney, F.J. #21909-1914 (Box 17, Folder 344)
  - Hew-Hi (Box 17, Folder 345)
  - Hichborn, F. (Box 17, Folder 346)
  - Hoa-Hom (Box 17, Folder 347)
  - Hoo-Hou (Box 17, Folder 348)